ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements, 5780/075
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements
1907-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/075
11.5 cubic feet
8 linear feet
Collective Bargaining Agreements
Consists of agreements and contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and associations of garment manufacturers.
6323015
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
July 2011
EAD encoding:
Cheryl Beredo, July 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Scope and Contents
Consists of agreements and contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and associations of garment manufacturers.
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
Related Materials
5780. ILGWU records
5780/075mf. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements. Microfilm
5780/085. ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files
5780/145. ILGWU. Association Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/146. ILGWU. Master Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/147. ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/158. ILGWU. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/191. ILGWU. Association Contracts
5780/202. ILGWU. Operations Department. Collective Bargaining Agreements
General
"Permanent deposit"
Arrangement
Agreements are arranged in alphabetical order by employer.
Women's clothing industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- New York (State) -- New York; Collective labor agreements -- United States; Industrial relations -- New York (State) -- New York; Industrial relations -- United States
6323015
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., 1930-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Allied Underwear Association, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agreements. American Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1916-1927 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers, Inc., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Association of Cloak and Suit Manufacturers of Seattle, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agreements. Association of Piped Buttonhole Manufacturers, Inc., 1946-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Agreements. The Belt Association, Inc., 1938-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Agreements. Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Agreements. Chicago Dress and Skirt Manufacturers Association, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Chicago Joint Board, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Children's' Dress, Infants' Wear, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Agreements. Cloak Drivers and Helpers Union, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agreements. Coat and Suit Group of Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Association (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Agreements. Dress Manufacturers' Guild of Toronto, Inc., 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Agreements. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors' Association, Inc., 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agreements. Infants' and Children's' Coat Association, Inc., 1940-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agreements. Joint Board of the Cloak, Suit and Skirtmakers' Unions of Philadelphia, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union, 1926-1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Agreements. Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers' Union, 1917-1945 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Agreements. The Lingerie Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc., 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Agreements. Merchant Ladies' Garment Association, 1924-1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Agreements. Montreal Dress Manufacturers' Guild, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Agreements. National Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1937-1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Agreements. Needle Trades Employers' Association, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Agreements. Negligee Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Agreements. Popular Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Agreements. Sportswear and Cotton Garment Workers, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Agreements. Toronto Cloak Manufacturers' Association, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Agreements. Underwear and White Goods Workers' Union, 1923-1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Agreements. United Ladies' Garments Manufacturers Association, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Agreements. United Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Agreements. Waterproof Garment Workers' Union, 1946-1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Agreements. ILGWU Miscellaneous, 1924-1950 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- California Industrial Welfare Commission. Changes in the Labor Code, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- California, Los Angeles. Court Cases, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- National Labor Relations Board. IGLWU v. Dolly Myers, Inc. and ILGWU v. Olympic Garments Company, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., 1951-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Allied Underwear Association, Inc., 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Agreements. Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Agreements. American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1929-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers, Inc., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Agreements. Association of Dress Manufacturers, Inc., 1925-1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Agreements. Association of Manufactures of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies Garments, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Agreements. Baltimore Clothing Manufacturers, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Agreements. Bonnaz, Embroideries, Tucking, Pleating and Allied Crafts Union, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Chicago Association of Dress Manufacturers, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Agreements. Children's' Dress, House Dress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, 1938-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Agreements. Cleveland Garment Manufacturers' Association, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Agreements. Cotton Garment Manufacturers of New York, Inc., 1923 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Agreements. Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association, 1913-1919 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Agreements. Fur Trimming Manufacturers Association, 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Agreements. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors' Association, Inc., 1950-1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Agreements. Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc., 1942-1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Agreements. ILGWU with Jonathan Logan, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Agreements. ILGWU with Local 122 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Agreements. IGLWU with Local 392, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Agreements. ILGWU with Maidenform, Inc., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Agreements. Infants' and Children's' Coat Association, Inc., 1937-1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Agreements. Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc., 1937-1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Agreements. Industrial Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association, 1924-1929 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Coat, Suit and Allied Garment Workers' Unions, 1973-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union [folder 2 of 2], 1943-1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Agreements. Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers Union, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Agreements. Kansas City Garment Manufacturers Association (Sportswear Group), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Agreements. Kenrose Manufacturing Company, 1950-1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Agreements. The Lingerie Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc., 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Agreements. Manufacturers' Council of the Ladies' Cloak and suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, Inc., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Agreements. Merchants' Ladies Garment Association, Inc., 1929-1948 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Agreements. Montreal Dress Manufacturers' Guild, 1942-1956 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Agreements. Montreal Dress and Sportswear Manufacturers' Guild, 1966-1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Agreements. National Association of Blouse Manufactures' Inc., 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Agreements. National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Agreements. National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association, Inc., 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Agreements. National Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1953-1973 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Agreements. New York Coat and Suit Association, Inc., 1967-1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Agreements. Smoler Bros., Inc., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Agreements. Snow Suit, Skiwear, Leggings and Infants' Novelty Wear Workers' Union, 1949-1964 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Agreements. Supak and Sons Manufacturing Corp., 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Agreements. United Better Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Agreements. United Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc., 1954-1970 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Agreements. Waterproof Garment Workers' Union, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Miscellaneous, 1944-1950 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Agreements. Allied Underwear Association, Inc., 1935-1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, 1913-1917 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Agreements. Boston, Miscellaneous, 1920-1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Boston Ladies' Garment Manufacturers' Association, 1912-1913 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Boston Ladies' Garment Manufacturers' Association and Dress and Waist Manufacturers, 1913- 1916 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Agreements. City of Boston, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Agreements. Cotton Garment Manufacturers of New York, Inc., 1913-1928 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Agreements. Knitgoods Workers Union, 1939-1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Agreements. The Lingerie Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc., 1931-1941 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Merchant Ladies Garment Association, 1929-1932 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Montreal, 1937-1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Agreements. National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1936 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Agreements. Negligee Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1933-1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Agreements. New York Market Coat and Suit Industry, Vol. I, 1910-1941 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Agreements. New York Market Coat and Suit Industry, Vol. II, 1924-1941 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Agreements. New York Market Coat and Suit Industry, Vol. III, 1916-1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Agreements. Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, 1937-1944 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Agreements. Underwear and White Goods Workers' Union, 1915-1934 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Agreements. United Underwear Contractors' Association, Inc., 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Agreements. Miscellaneous, Pre-1920, 1913-1920 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1930-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1930-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1930-1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Allied Underwear Association, Inc., 1947-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Agreements. American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1929-1932 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Agreements. Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers, Inc., 1953-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Agreements. Association of Dress Manufacturers, 1919-1932 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Agreements. Chicago Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1919-1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Agreements. Children's Dress, Infants' Wear, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, 1946-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association, 1916-1924 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Forest Manufacturing Company, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Agreements. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Undergarment Association, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Agreements. ILGWU, 1913-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Agreements. Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc., 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Agreements. Italian Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union [Italian] (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloakmakers' Union, 1943-1948 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt, Dress and Reefer Makers' Unions, 1924-1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit and Allied Garment Workers' Unions, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Agreements. Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers' Union, 1933-1951 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Agreements. Lingerie Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc., 1945-1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Agreements. The Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Agreements. The Montreal Dress and Sportswear Manufacturers' Guild [French], 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Agreements. National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Agreements. National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1936-1961 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Agreements. National Skirt Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1943-1967 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Agreements. National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association, Inc., 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Agreements. The Negligee Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc., 1945-1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Agreements. Plastic Products Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Agreements. Pleaters, Stitchers and Embroidery Manufacturers Association, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Agreements. Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1936-1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Agreements. Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1936-1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Agreements. San Francisco Joint Board, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Agreements. Dress Contract Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1919 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Dressmakers' Joint Council, 1916-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agreements. Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc., 1943-1954 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Dress and Waistmakers' Union [folder 1 of 2], 1913-1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Dress and Waistmakers' Union [folder 2 of 2], 1913-1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Agreements. National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1938-1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Agreements. National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1936-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Agreements. New York Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Agreements. Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Snow Suit, Skiwear, Leggings and Infants' Novelty Wear Workers' Union, 1947-1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Agreements. The Undergarment Accessories Association, Inc., 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Agreements. United Association of Dress Manufacturers, Inc., 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Agreements. United Better Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1941-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Agreements. United Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Agreements. United Popular Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1941-1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Agreements. Waterproof Products Manufacturing Association, Inc., 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Agreements. ILGWU Miscellaneous, 1933-1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Agreements. Amalgamated Manufacturers' Council, 1930-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agreements. American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Agreements. Designers' Guild of Ladies' Apparel, Local 30, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Dress Manufacturers' Guild of Toronto, Inc., 1939-1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Embroidery Workers Union, 1914-1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Agreements. ILGWU Local 14,83,68 and 92, 1935-1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Agreements. ILGWU Local 72, 1937-1948 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Agreements. ILGWU Local 199, 1947-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Agreements. ILGWU Miscellaneous, 1925-1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc., 1926-1940 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Joint Board Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions, 1910-1916 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Agreements. Joint Board of the Cloak, Skirt, Dress and Reefer Makers' Unions, 1910-1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Dress and Waistmakers' Union of Greater New York, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Agreements. Knitgoods Workers Union, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Agreements. Manufacturers' Council, 1949-1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Agreements. Merchants' Ladies' Garment Association, Inc., 1932-1940 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Agreements. Miscellaneous, 1929-1954 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Agreements. National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Agreements. Toronto Cloak Contractors Association, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Agreements. Toronto Cloak Jobbers Association, 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Agreements. The Toronto Cloak Manufacturers' Association, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1934-1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Agreements. The Toronto Cloak Manufacturers' Association, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1934-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Agreements. The Toronto Cloak Manufacturers' Protective Association, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Agreements. The Toronto Joint Board, 1934-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Agreements. Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, 1937-1945 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Agreements. The United Brotherhood of Cloakmakers, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., 1938-1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Allied Underwear Association, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Agreements. American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1929-1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Children's' Dress, House Dress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors' Association, Inc., 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Agreements. Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Agreements. Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc., 1926-1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Agreements. Infants' and Children's' Coat Association, Inc., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Agreements. Infants' and Children's' Novelties Association, 1947-1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union, 1943-1948 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers Union [folder 1 of 2], 1936-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Agreements. Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers Union [folder 2 of 2], 1936-1958 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Agreements. The Lingerie Manufacturers' Association of New York, Inc., 1953-1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Agreements. Maidenform, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Agreements. Merchants' Ladies' Garment Association, Inc., 1924-1940 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Agreements. National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1938-1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Agreements. National Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1943-1961 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Agreements. The Negligee Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1943-1956 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Agreements. New York Raincoat Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Agreements. The Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc., 1939-1944 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Agreements. The Snowsuit, Skiwear, Leggings and Infants' Novelty Wear Workers' Union [folder 1 of 2], 1943- 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Agreements. The Snowsuit, Skiwear, Leggings and Infants' Novelty Wear Workers' Union [folder 2 of 2], 1943- 1964 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Agreements. Sportswear and Miscellaneous Apparel Contractors Association, Inc., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Agreements. United Association of Dress Manufacturers, 1925-1938 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Agreements. United Better Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Agreements. United Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Agreements. United Ladies' Garments Manufacturers Association, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 27)